Lincoln Filene Center Records UA018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1944 -- 1997; 1950 -- 1997; UA018.001; 32.25 Linear Feet
  - Past Programs, 1959 -- 1975; UA018.001.015
    - Current Affairs, 1968; UA018.001.034.00006 (Box 34)
      Newsweek
    - Economics Conference, 1965; UA018.001.034.00007 (Box 34)
    - Ecumenical Committee, 1973; UA018.001.034.00008 (Box 34)
      Crime Prevention, Legal Studies
    - Educational Renewal, 1972; UA018.001.034.00009 (Box 34)
    - Education and Race Relations, 1965; UA018.001.034.00010 (Box 34)
    - Environmental / Special Studies, 1971; UA018.001.034.00011 (Box 34)
    - Environmental Crises, 1971; UA018.001.034.00012 (Box 34)
    - ERA, 1972; UA018.001.035.00001 (Box 35)
    - Experimental Social Studies: Medford, 1973; UA018.001.035.00002 (Box 35)
    - Law in Education, 1972; UA018.001.035.00003 (Box 35)
      Ex College Material
    - EXP 89 - Environment, 1971; UA018.001.035.00004 (Box 35)
      A Field Course for Teachers
    - Fletcher School, 1966; UA018.001.035.00005 (Box 35)
    - Flexible Campus, 1971 -- 1972; UA018.001.035.00006 (Box 35)
    - Flexible Campus, 1971 -- 1973; UA018.001.035.00007 (Box 35)
    - Focal Point, 1962; UA018.001.035.00008 (Box 35)
    - Gerald Ford Budget, 1975; UA018.001.035.00009 (Box 35)
    - Futuristic, 1973; UA018.001.035.00010 (Box 35)
    - Group 10, 1973; UA018.001.036.00001 (Box 36)
    - Heritage Day, 1960 -- 1965; UA018.001.036.00002 (Box 36)
    - Higher Education Project, 1966; UA018.001.036.00003 (Box 36)
    - Hingham, 1970 -- 1973; UA018.001.036.00004 (Box 36)
    - Intergroup Relations, 1968 -- 1972; UA018.001.036.00005 (Box 36)
    - Internships, 1972; UA018.001.036.00006 (Box 36)
      Berman
    - Invitational Conference, 1969; UA018.001.036.00007 (Box 36)
    - Human Relations Seminar, 1970; UA018.001.036.00008 (Box 36)
      Duval County, Florida
    - K-6 Project, 1967; UA018.001.036.00009 (Box 36)
    - Labor Management, 1974; UA018.001.036.00010 (Box 36)
      Labor Management Relations in the United States: Some Lessons and Perspectives for the 1970s
    - Law Program, 1971; UA018.001.036.00011 (Box 36)
      Somerville
    - Law in Social Studies, 1972 -- 1973; UA018.001.036.00012 (Box 36)
    - Lexington, 1966; UA018.001.036.00013 (Box 36)
    - Manchester, 1970; UA018.001.036.00014 (Box 36)
    - Massachusetts Legislature, UA018.001.036.00015 (Box 36)
      121 Information Kit
    - Massachusetts Viewpoint, 1962 -- 1966; UA018.001.036.00016 (Box 36)
    - Mayor's Conference on Regional Issues, 1969; UA018.001.037.00001 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
      Referendum, Mayor's Council on Regional Issues, Task Force on Education, Executive Committee
    - MCUU, 1970 -- 1971; UA018.001.037.00002 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - MCUU, 1968 -- 1969; UA018.001.037.00003 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - MCUU, 1968 -- 1970; UA018.001.037.00004 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - MCUU, 1971 -- 1972; UA018.001.037.00005 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - MCUU -BRA, 1970; UA018.001.037.00006 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - MCUU - Correspondence, 1970 -- 1971; UA018.001.037.00007 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - MCUU - V.E.T. Committee, 1968 -- 1971; UA018.001.037.00008 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - MCUU - Tutorial, 1969 -- 1971; UA018.001.037.00009 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - MCUU - Impact Survey, 1970 -- 1971; UA018.001.038.00001 (Box 38)
    - Medford High and Minorities in Contemporary American Society, 1970; UA018.001.038.00002 (Box 38)
      Doreen Blanc
    - Meserve, Robert, 1972; UA018.001.038.00003 (Box 38)
      President, American Bar Association
    - Metropolitan Education Advisory Council, 1973; UA018.001.038.00004 (Box 38)
    - Mosaic Boston, 1974; UA018.001.038.00005 (Box 38)
    - Multicultural Factors, 1973; UA018.001.038.00006 (Box 38)
    - NATO Seminar, 1972; UA018.001.038.00007 (Box 38)
    - New England History Teachers' Association, 1968; UA018.001.038.00008 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Negro in American Life, 1963 -- 1965; UA018.001.038.00009 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Newton, Warren J.H. Seminar, UA018.001.038.00010 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Newton, 1961; UA018.001.038.00011 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Newton, 1962 -- 1965; UA018.001.039.00001 (Box 39)
    - Non Public Schools, 1970; UA018.001.039.00002 (Box 39)
    - New England Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1969; UA018.001.039.00003 (Box 39)
      Urban Orientation Seminar
    - Northeastern States, 1969 -- 1971; UA018.001.039.00004 (Box 39)
    - Philadelphia, 1973; UA018.001.039.00005 (Box 39)
    - The Politician, 1962 -- 1963; UA018.001.039.00006 (Box 39)
    - Power in the City, 1966 -- 1967; UA018.001.039.00007 (Box 39)
    - Practical Politics, 1962; UA018.001.039.00008 (Box 39)
    - Tufts - Roxbury Project, 1966 -- 1967; UA018.001.039.00009 (Box 39)
    - Proctor Academy, 1974 -- 1975; UA018.001.039.00010 (Box 39)
    - Rhode Island, 1968; UA018.001.039.00011 (Box 39)
    - Rhode Island Board of Education, 1969; UA018.001.039.00012 (Box 39)
    - Report on Operations and Accomplishment, 1974; UA018.001.039.00013 (Box 39)
    - Seminar Lectures, 1960 -- 1961; UA018.001.039.00014 (Box 39)
      Drafts
    - September Conference, 1962; UA018.001.040.00001 (Box 40)
    - Simulation Exercise, UA018.001.040.00002 (Box 40)
    - Social Studies Specialists, 1969; UA018.001.040.00003 (Box 40)
    - Somerville Community Council, 1959 -- 1962; UA018.001.040.00004 (Box 40)
    - Somerville Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1971; UA018.001.040.00005 (Box 40)
    - Somerville Seminar, 1969 -- 1970; UA018.001.040.00006 (Box 40)
    - State and Local Finances, 1975; UA018.001.040.00007 (Box 40)
    - State Social Studies Specialists, 1966; UA018.001.040.00008 (Box 40)
    - Taft Institute, 1973; UA018.001.040.00009 (Box 40)
    - Taft Institute, 1972; UA018.001.040.00010 (Box 40)
    - Taft Institute, 1971; UA018.001.040.00011 (Box 40)
    - Taunton Black Studies, 1970; UA018.001.040.00012 (Box 40)
    - Tewksbury Seminars, 1968 -- 1970; UA018.001.040.00013 (Box 40)
    - TEE Forum: Franklin Park, 1975; UA018.001.040.00014 (Box 40)
    - Trustee Fall Forum: Mystic, Aberjona, 1974; UA018.001.040.00015 (Box 40)
    - 21" Classroom, 1967; UA018.001.040.00016 (Box 40)
    - Upward Bound, 1966 -- 1967; UA018.001.041.00001 (Box 41)
    - Whose Decision?, 1961; UA018.001.041.00002 (Box 41)
    - World Affairs Conference, 1967; UA018.001.041.00003 (Box 41)
    - Youth Conference, 1971; UA018.001.041.00004 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Youth Conference, 1970; UA018.001.041.00005 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Youth Conference, 1969; UA018.001.041.00006 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Youth Conference, 1967; UA018.001.041.00007 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Youth Conference, 1966; UA018.001.041.00008 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Youth Conference, 1964; UA018.001.041.00009 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Youth Planning Council, 1967; UA018.001.041.00010 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Youth Speaks Its Mind, 1959; UA018.001.041.00011 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Youth and Adult Values Study, 1966; UA018.001.041.00012 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
      New England School Development Council
    - New Frontiers, 1968; UA018.001.041.00013 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - New Frontiers, 1964 -- 1965; UA018.001.041.00014 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - Newsweek, 1972; UA018.001.041.00015 (Box data_value_missing_ba64368924dd34cc1a3691b0f2ba0ceb)
    - New Schools for Poor, 1966; UA018.001.042.00001 (Box 42)
      for Citizen's Crusade against Poverty
    - Tufts - Northeast Youth Citizenship Conference, 1961; UA018.001.042.00002 (Box 42)
    - No Hope for Boston Schools?, 1968; UA018.001.042.00003 (Box 42)
    - On the Defense of the Community, 1970; UA018.001.042.00004 (Box 42)
      an examination of student radicalism
    - On Quality in Education, 1970; UA018.001.042.00005 (Box 42)
    - Our Street, UA018.001.042.00006 (Box 42)
    - Outside the Ivy, 1967; UA018.001.042.00007 (Box 42)
    - Pictures and Bridges, 1969; UA018.001.042.00008 (Box 42)
    - P.O.D., 1963; UA018.001.042.00009 (Box 42)
      Problems of Democracy Series, Houghton Mifflin
    - Political Reality in Childhood, 1963; UA018.001.042.00010 (Box 42)
    - Political Significance of European Integration, 1970; UA018.001.042.00011 (Box 42)
    - Poor, Schools, Equal Protection, 1968; UA018.001.042.00012 (Box 42)
    - Popular Support for Business Policy, 1962; UA018.001.042.00013 (Box 42)
    - Postmortem of Our Dreams, 1967; UA018.001.042.00014 (Box 42)
    - Poverty, Education, Race Relations: Studies and Proposals, 1966; UA018.001.042.00015; Kvaraceus, William C.; Gibson, John S.; Curtin, Thomas J. (Box 42)
      Lincoln Filene Center
    - Practical Political Action, 1962; UA018.001.042.00016 (Box 42)
    - Prisons, 1972; UA018.001.042.00017 (Box 42)
    - Problems and Practices, 1966; UA018.001.042.00018 (Box 42)
    - Process Approach, 1966; UA018.001.042.00019 (Box 42)
    - Proposed Aid for Civic Education, 1970; UA018.001.042.00020 (Box 42)
  - Nine States, 1944 -- 1969; UA018.001.016
    - Nine States Program, 1960; UA018.001.042.00021 (Box 42)
    - Nine States Bylaws, 1964; UA018.001.042.00022 (Box 42)
    - Nine States Coordinating Council, 1969; UA018.001.042.00023 (Box 42)
    - Nine States: Correspondence, 1961 -- 1964; UA018.001.042.00024 (Box 42)
    - Nine States: Danforth Appeal, 1962 -- 1963; UA018.001.042.00025 (Box 42)
    - Nine States: Ford Foundation Appeal, 1962; UA018.001.042.00026 (Box 42)
    - Nine States: Commissioners, 1960 -- 1967; UA018.001.043.00001 (Box 43)
    - Nine States: Connecticut, 1963; UA018.001.043.00002 (Box 43)
    - Nine States: Maine, 1963 -- 1964; UA018.001.043.00003 (Box 43)
    - Nine States: New Hampshire, 1962 -- 1964; UA018.001.043.00004 (Box 43)
    - Nine States: New Jersey, 1961 -- 1963; UA018.001.043.00005 (Box 43)
    - Nine States: Massachusetts, 1958 -- 1965; UA018.001.043.00006 (Box 43)
    - Mahoney, John, 1944 -- 1964; UA018.001.043.00007 (Box 43)
    - Nine States: New York, 1961 -- 1964; UA018.001.043.00008 (Box 43)
    - Nine States: Vermont, 1962 -- 1963; UA018.001.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - Ford Motor Co. Foundation, 1949 -- 1964; UA018.001.017
    - Ford Study: Correspondence, 1958 -- 1959; UA018.001.043.00010 (Box 43)
    - Ford Study: Finances, 1958 -- 1959; UA018.001.043.00011 (Box 43)
    - Ford Motor Company Foundation, 1951 -- 1962; UA018.001.043.00012 (Box 43)
    - Ford Study: Interdisciplinary Study Group, 1958 -- 1959; UA018.001.043.00013 (Box 43)
    - Ford Study: Working Papers, 1958; UA018.001.043.00014 (Box 43)
    - Ford Study: New Perspectives, 1956; UA018.001.043.00015 (Box 43)
    - Ford Foundation, 1952 -- 1953; UA018.001.043.00016 (Box 43)
    - Ford Story, 1953 -- 1956; UA018.001.044.00001 (Box 44)
    - Falk Foundation, 1950; UA018.001.044.00002 (Box 44)
    - Fund for the Republic, 1954; UA018.001.044.00003 (Box 44)
    - Grant Foundation, 1949 -- 1950; UA018.001.044.00004 (Box 44)
    - Richardson Foundation, 1956; UA018.001.044.00005 (Box 44)
    - Workshop (Summer), 1962 -- 1963; UA018.001.044.00006 (Box 44)
    - Workshop (Summer), 1964; UA018.001.044.00007 (Box 44)
      Part 1
    - Workshop (Summer), 1964; UA018.001.044.00008 (Box 44)
      Part 2
  - Boston Schools Project, 1972 -- 1982; UA018.001.018
    - Boston Schools - Pairings, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.044.00009 (Box 44)
    - Boston Schools - Chapter 636, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.044.00010 (Box 44)
    - Support for Boston Schools, 1978 -- 1980; UA018.001.044.00011 (Box 44)
    - City Hall, 1977; UA018.001.045.00001 (Box 45)
    - CityWide Coordinating Council, 1977 -- 1978; UA018.001.045.00002 (Box 45)
    - CityWide Coordinating Council, 1976 -- 1978; UA018.001.045.00003 (Box 45)
    - CityWide Coordinating Council, 1977; UA018.001.045.00004 (Box 45)
      Jim Breeden
    - CityWide Educational Project, 1977; UA018.001.045.00005 (Box 45)
    - Tri-Lateral Council, 1975 -- 1980; UA018.001.045.00006 (Box 45)
    - Tri-Lateral Council, 1975 -- 1976; UA018.001.046.00001 (Box 46)
    - Contracts, 1976 -- 1979; UA018.001.046.00002 (Box 46)
    - Contract Amendments, 1976; UA018.001.046.00003 (Box 46)
    - TItle III, 1974; UA018.001.046.00004 (Box 46)
    - Action Grant, 1978; UA018.001.046.00005 (Box 46)
    - Report #4, 1975; UA018.001.046.00006 (Box 46)
    - Executive Committee, 1976 -- 1979; UA018.001.046.00007 (Box 46)
    - Boston, 1976; UA018.001.046.00008 (Box 46)
    - Chapter 636, 1977 -- 1980; UA018.001.046.00009 (Box 46)
    - ESAA, 1973 -- 1979; UA018.001.046.00010 (Box 46)
    - ESAA, 1979; UA018.001.046.00011 (Box 46)
    - ESAA, 1977 -- 1978; UA018.001.046.00012 (Box 46)
    - Interim Report, 1976; UA018.001.046.00013 (Box 46)
    - Kindergarten, 1977; UA018.001.046.00014 (Box 46)
    - Evaluation Report, 1976 -- 1977; UA018.001.047.00001 (Box 47)
    - CDAC, 1978 -- 1979; UA018.001.047.00002 (Box 47)
    - CDAC, 1975 -- 1976; UA018.001.047.00003 (Box 47)
    - CDAC, 1976 -- 1977; UA018.001.047.00004 (Box 47)
    - CDAC, 1979 -- 1980; UA018.001.047.00005 (Box 47)
    - CDAC, 1978; UA018.001.047.00006 (Box 47)
    - CDAC, 1977 -- 1978; UA018.001.047.00007 (Box 47)
    - CDAC, 1979 -- 1980; UA018.001.047.00008 (Box 47)
    - Simmons College, 1975; UA018.001.048.00001 (Box 48)
      Status Report
    - Contracts, 1974 -- 1975; UA018.001.048.00002 (Box 48)
    - Court Orders, 1977 -- 1980; UA018.001.048.00003 (Box 48)
    - Budget Proposals, 1976 -- 1977; UA018.001.048.00004 (Box 48)
    - Suffolk, 1976 -- 1977; UA018.001.049.00001 (Box 49)
    - Tufts, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.049.00002 (Box 49)
    - UMass Boston, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.049.00003 (Box 49)
    - Wellesley, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.049.00004 (Box 49)
    - Wheelock, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.049.00005 (Box 49)
    - Milton Academy, 1975; UA018.001.049.00006 (Box 49)
    - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance, 1975; UA018.001.049.00007 (Box 49)
    - Thompson Academy, 1975; UA018.001.049.00008 (Box 49)
    - Administrative Circular, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.049.00009 (Box 49)
    - Associated Foundation of Greater Boston, 1975; UA018.001.049.00010 (Box 49)
    - Boston Municipal Research Bureau, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.049.00011 (Box 49)
    - Coordinators / Universities, 1975 -- 1980; UA018.001.049.00012 (Box 49)
    - Steering Committee, 1975; UA018.001.050.00001 (Box 50)
    - Steering Committee, 1976; UA018.001.050.00002 (Box 50)
    - Steering Committee, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.050.00003 (Box 50)
    - Steering Committee, 1977 -- 1978; UA018.001.050.00004 (Box 50)
    - Steering Committee, 1979 -- 1980; UA018.001.050.00005 (Box 50)
    - Steering Committee, 1975 -- 1979; UA018.001.050.00006 (Box 50)
    - Steering Committee, 1975 -- 1979; UA018.001.050.00007 (Box 50)
      Minutes
    - Steering Committee, 1976; UA018.001.050.00008 (Box 50)
      Business
    - Faculty Advisory Committee, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.050.00009 (Box 50)
    - Title IV: Application, 1973 -- 1978; UA018.001.050.00010 (Box 50)
    - Boston School Committee, 1975 -- 1979; UA018.001.051.00001 (Box 51)
    - Boston School Department, 1980 -- 1981; UA018.001.051.00002 (Box 51)
    - Boston School Department, 1979; UA018.001.051.00003 (Box 51)
      Proposal
    - Middle Schools Contract, 1979; UA018.001.051.00004 (Box 51)
    - Fahey-Hunt, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.051.00005 (Box 51)
    - Chapter 636, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.051.00006 (Box 51)
    - Chapter 636, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.052.00001 (Box 52)
      Pairs
    - Chapter 636, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.052.00002 (Box 52)
    - Chapter 636, 1974 -- 1979; UA018.001.052.00003 (Box 52)
    - Chapter 636, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.052.00004 (Box 52)
    - Code of Discipline, 1979 -- 1982; UA018.001.052.00005 (Box 52)
    - Correspondence, 1978 -- 1980; UA018.001.052.00006 (Box 52)
    - Correspondence, 1977; UA018.001.052.00007 (Box 52)
    - Correspondence, 1977; UA018.001.052.00008 (Box 52)
    - Correspondence, 1976; UA018.001.053.00001 (Box 53)
    - Correspondence, 1976; UA018.001.053.00002 (Box 53)
    - Correspondence, 1975; UA018.001.053.00003 (Box 53)
    - Correspondence, 1974 -- 1979; UA018.001.053.00004 (Box 53)
      Incoming
    - Helen Bond, Cleveland, 1975 -- 1979; UA018.001.053.00005 (Box 53)
    - Jeptha Carrell, 1978 -- 1980; UA018.001.053.00006 (Box 53)
    - Heinz Bondy, 1977 -- 1979; UA018.001.054.00001 (Box 54)
    - Boyer / Berry, 1973 -- 1979; UA018.001.054.00002 (Box 54)
    - Correspondence, 1980; UA018.001.054.00003 (Box 54)
      Northeastern / Barbara Burke
    - John Coakley, 1979; UA018.001.054.00004 (Box 54)
    - David Colton, 1979 -- 1980; UA018.001.054.00005 (Box 54)
    - Walter Dean / Jane Echelson, 1979; UA018.001.054.00006 (Box 54)
    - John Driscoll, 1976 -- 1978; UA018.001.054.00007 (Box 54)
    - Thomas Fulham, UA018.001.054.00008 (Box 54)
    - Joyce Grant-Gray, 1978 -- 1980; UA018.001.054.00009 (Box 54)
    - Correspondence, 1977 -- 1980; UA018.001.054.00010 (Box 54)
      Hazelton - Held - Holmes - Hunt - Harriman
    - Correspondence, 1976 -- 1979; UA018.001.054.00011 (Box 54)
      Lamphere - Lombardi - Lowell
    - Correspondence, 1976 -- 1979; UA018.001.054.00012 (Box 54)
      Meade - Meachem - Minter - "Tip" O'Neill
    - Correspondence, 1977 -- 1978; UA018.001.054.00013 (Box 54)
      Paintor - Parham - Patterson - Perullo
    - Evaluation Reports, 1979; UA018.001.054.00014 (Box 54)
    - Correspondence, 1978 -- 1980; UA018.001.054.00015 (Box 54)
      Stannard - Stewart - Wood - Walsh
    - Code of Discipline, 1976 -- 1978; UA018.001.055.00001 (Box 55)
    - ESAA, 1976 -- 1979; UA018.001.055.00002 (Box 55)
    - Executive Committee, 1975; UA018.001.055.00003 (Box 55)
    - Funding Proposals, 1975; UA018.001.055.00004 (Box 55)
    - Funding, 1977; UA018.001.055.00005 (Box 55)
    - Funding, 1978; UA018.001.055.00006 (Box 55)
    - Correspondence, 1976 -- 1978; UA018.001.055.00007 (Box 55)
      Newell Flather
    - Financial Aid, 1978; UA018.001.055.00008 (Box 55)
    - Flexible Campus, 1973 -- 1975; UA018.001.055.00009 (Box 55)
    - Carnegie Corporation, 1979; UA018.001.055.00010 (Box 55)
      CC of New York
    - Ford Foundation, 1975 -- 1980; UA018.001.055.00011 (Box 55)
    - Freedom House, 1975 -- 1980; UA018.001.055.00012 (Box 55)
    - Fred Glimp, 1975 -- 1979; UA018.001.056.00001 (Box 56)
    - Interim Evaluations, 1977 -- 1978; UA018.001.056.00002 (Box 56)
    - Kindergarten Plan, 1977; UA018.001.056.00003 (Box 56)
    - Court Orders, 1976 -- 1977; UA018.001.056.00004 (Box 56)
    - LINC Program, 1979; UA018.001.056.00005 (Box 56)
    - Master Copies, 1976 -- 1979; UA018.001.056.00006 (Box 56)
    - Master Copies, 1975 -- 1976; UA018.001.056.00007 (Box 56)
    - Metropolitan Education Center, 1975; UA018.001.057.00001 (Box 57)
    - National League of Cities, 1978; UA018.001.057.00002 (Box 57)
    - News Releases and Articles, 1974 -- 1977; UA018.001.057.00003 (Box 57)
    - Occupational - Vocational Education, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.057.00004 (Box 57)
    - John Doherty, 1978; UA018.001.057.00005 (Box 57)
    - Clark Fisher, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.057.00006 (Box 57)
    - Personnel, 1975; UA018.001.057.00007 (Box 57)
    - Massachusetts Interns, 1975; UA018.001.057.00008 (Box 57)
    - Publications, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.058.00001 (Box 58)
    - Publications, 1972 -- 1978; UA018.001.058.00002 (Box 58)
    - School Volunteers, 1975; UA018.001.058.00003 (Box 58)
    - College Scholarships, 1977; UA018.001.058.00004 (Box 58)
    - Teaching Center, 1977 -- 1978; UA018.001.058.00005 (Box 58)
    - TDR, 1975; UA018.001.058.00006 (Box 58)
    - USC, 1975 -- 1976; UA018.001.058.00007 (Box 58)
      Joint Educational Project
    - Washington Reports, 1976; UA018.001.058.00008 (Box 58)
    - School Committee, 1978; UA018.001.059.00001 (Box 59)
    - Antioch, 1975 -- 1976; UA018.001.059.00002 (Box 59)
    - Boston College, 1975 -- 1977; UA018.001.059.00003 (Box 59)
    - Boston College, 1977 -- 1978; UA018.001.059.00004 (Box 59)
    - Boston College, 1976 -- 1978; UA018.001.059.00005 (Box 59)
    - Boston State, 1976 -- 1977; UA018.001.060.00001 (Box 60)
    - Boston State, 1979; UA018.001.060.00002 (Box 60)
    - Boston University, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.060.00003 (Box 60)
    - Brandeis, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.060.00004 (Box 60)
    - Bunker Hill Community College, 1975 -- 1978; UA018.001.060.00005 (Box 60)
    - Bunker Hill Community College, 1975 -- 1976; UA018.001.061.00001 (Box 61)
    - Curry College, 1976 -- 1980; UA018.001.061.00002 (Box 61)
    - Emerson, 1975 -- 1980; UA018.001.061.00003 (Box 61)
    - Emmanuel, 1976; UA018.001.061.00004 (Box 61)
    - Harvard, 1976 -- 1977; UA018.001.061.00005 (Box 61)
    - Lesley, 1975 -- 1979; UA018.001.061.00006 (Box 61)
    - Mass. College of Art, 1976 -- 1978; UA018.001.061.00007 (Box 61)
    - Mass. College of Pharmacy, UA018.001.061.00008 (Box 61)
    - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance, 1975; UA018.001.061.00009 (Box 61)
    - MIT, 1976 -- 1978; UA018.001.062.00001 (Box 62)
    - Northeastern, 1976 -- 1977; UA018.001.062.00002 (Box 62)
    - Northeastern, 1975 -- 1979; UA018.001.062.00003 (Box 62)
    - Regis, 1977; UA018.001.062.00004 (Box 62)
    - MIT, 1975 -- 1976; UA018.001.063.00001 (Box 63)
    - CDAC, 1976 -- 1977; UA018.001.063.00002 (Box 63)
    - CDAC, 1975 -- 1976; UA018.001.063.00003 (Box 63)
    - Budgets - Proposals, 1977; UA018.001.063.00004 (Box 63)
    - Hearings, 1977 -- 1980; UA018.001.063.00005 (Box 63)
    - Proposals - Reports, 1977; UA018.001.064.00001 (Box 64)
- Publications, 1952 -- 1998; UA018.003; 2.65 Linear Feet; 58 Volumes; 12 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains monograph and irregular serial publications produced by the Lincoln Filene Center. Serial publications, such as newsletters, are cataloged as separate collections under the title of the publication, for example, the LFC Report.
  This series is arranged as found.
  - Cable, Public Television and the Interactive Viewer, 1983; UA018.003.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - Practical Political Action (Teacher's Guide), 1962; UA018.003.067.00002 (Box 67)
  - Captialism - Way of Freedom (Teacher's Guide), 1952; UA018.003.067.00003 (Box 67)
  - What does Citizenship Mean?, 1961; UA018.003.067.00004; Dunham, Paul C. (Box 67)
    The Foundations of Citizenship in Law and Government.
  - The Isms and You, 1952; UA018.003.067.00005 (Box 67)
  - They Made a Nation, 1952; UA018.003.067.00006 (Box 67)
  - Who Says So?, 1952; UA018.003.067.00007 (Box 67)
  - Citizenship and a Free Society: Education for the Future, 1980; UA018.003.067.00008 (Box 67)
  - Conflict in the Middle East (Teacher's Manual), 1969; UA018.003.067.00009 (Box 67)
  - Final Technical Report on the Institute for Foreign Policy Institute for Secondary School Teachers, 1968; UA018.003.067.00010 (Box 67)
  - Educational Teleconferencing in Massachusetts: Project Evaluation for the MA Corporation for Educational Telecommunications' "Invisible Experiences: Looking Back and Ahead", 1987; UA018.003.067.00011 (Box 67)